<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Books - Category - Chloe's study hub</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/categories/books/</link><description>Books - Category - Chloe's study hub</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lehanget154.github.io/categories/books/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DO OVER - Jon Acuff</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/do-over/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/do-over/</guid><description>Đến với DO OVER, bạn sẽ học được những điều sau:
Xây dựng tài khoản tiết kiệm sự nghiệp đáng giá hàng tỷ đồng Áp dụng tài khoản này vào quá trình tái tạo sự nghiệp mà bạn luôn mong muốn TÀI KHOẢN TIẾT KIỆM SỰ NGHIỆP Mở đầu cuốn sách, tác giả đã nêu lên một định nghĩa khá thú vị “CAREER SAVINGS ACCOUNT”, tạm dịch TÀI KHOẢN TIẾT KIỆM SỰ NGHIỆP.</description></item><item><title>THE HR ESSENTIAL HANDBOOK</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/hr-essential-handbook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/hr-essential-handbook/</guid><description>Chương 1: Strategic HR Organizational strategy: direction, plan to implement the strategy (future&amp;rsquo;s path, resources) Organizational resources: intellectual capital, products, financial capital, human capital The strategic planning process begins by determining what the organization wants to achieve throughout a reasonable period of time: 1 - 2 - 3 - 5 - 10 years Develop a strategic plan: Mission: Establish why the organization exists, its mission. Vision: Define what you want the organization&amp;rsquo;s near future to be.</description></item><item><title>BẠN ĐẮT GIÁ BAO NHIÊU &amp; KHÍ CHẤT BAO NHIÊU, HẠNH PHÚC BẤY NHIÊU</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/ban-dat-gia-bao-nhieu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/ban-dat-gia-bao-nhieu/</guid><description>THỎA HIỆP không phải luôn là sự lựa chọn đúng đắn. Thỏa hiệp vì không có chính kiến, thỏa hiệp vì sợ người khác không hài lòng với mình, thỏa hiệp vì sợ mất đi mối quan hệ nào đó, thỏa hiệp vì yếu đuối. Đây là những lý do bạn sẽ không vui vẻ với cuộc sống của mình vì chọn cách thỏa hiệp thay vì đấu tranh.</description></item><item><title>HIRING AND KEEPING THE BEST PEOPLE</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/hiring-and-keeping-the-best-people/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/hiring-and-keeping-the-best-people/</guid><description>I/ Quy trình tuyển dụng thu hút người tài 1/ Xác định yêu cầu công việc a/ Trách nhiệm, nhiệm vụ chính liên quan đến công việc. Xem lại, đánh giá bảng mô tả công việc của người đang làm ở vị trí đó nếu có &amp;gt; Đây cũng là cơ hội đánh giá lại công việc cần tuyển dụng. b/ Yêu cầu cơ bản cần thiết để thực hiện công việc (học vấn, kinh nghiệm).</description></item><item><title>HOW TO CHOOSE YOUR CAREER - Onsen Swett Marden</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/how-to-choose-your-career/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/how-to-choose-your-career/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Mối hấp dẫn nhận lấy công việc mà mình không phù hợp chỉ vì được trả lương cao hơn một chút so với việc khác lúc ban đầu, trên hết, chính là nguyên cớ gây ra nhiều kết hợp không vững chắc nhất. Một khi bạn đã vững chỗ thì sẽ rất khó đánh đổi nó để tìm công việc lớn lao hơn, rất khó để quyết định bắt đầu lại từ nấc thang dưới cùng và sẽ mất thêm nhiều năm học tập, rèn luyện.</description></item><item><title>BOOK LIST</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/kindle-book-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/kindle-book-list/</guid><description>Nguồn tải sách Shared drive dtv.com libgen.is Facebook group Book list HR books Work rules - Laszlo Bock How to choose your career - Onsen Swett Marden Hiring and Keeping the Best People (Part 1)- Harvard Business Essentials Do over - Jon Acuff The HR essential handbook Why you? - James Reed Good to great - James C. Collins The HR Scorecard - Brian E. Becker, Mark A.</description></item><item><title>ĐỌC SÁCH SAO CHO HIỆU QUẢ</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/effective-reading/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/effective-reading/</guid><description>Chọn sách Đối với Văn học thì chọn sách đã xuất bản từ lâu, của những tác giả nổi tiếng, được đánh giá tốt. Đối với sách kĩ thuật thì chọn sách xuất bản, tái bản càng mới càng tốt. Không chọn sách dài lê thê, sách gây nhàm chán, khó đọc. Tuy nhiên sách ngắn, hời hợt cũng không nên chọn. Đọc những sách mà hướng con người về Chân - Thiện - Mỹ.</description></item><item><title>WORK RULES - LASLZO BOCK</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/work-rules/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/work-rules/</guid><description>Work rules 1: Become a founder Choose to think of yourself as a founder
Now act like one
Building an exceptional team or institution starts with a founder. But being a founder doesn’t mean starting a new company. It is within anyone’s grasp to be the founder and culture-creator of their own team, whether you are the first employee or joining a company that has existed for decades. Google was fortunate that our founders had such strong beliefs about the kind of company they wanted to create.</description></item></channel></rss>