<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Lifestyle - Category - Chloe's study hub</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/categories/lifestyle/</link><description>Lifestyle - Category - Chloe's study hub</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lehanget154.github.io/categories/lifestyle/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NHỮNG TRƯỜNG HỢP CHƯA NÊN ĐẦU TƯ</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/nhung-truong-hop-khong-nen-dau-tu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/nhung-truong-hop-khong-nen-dau-tu/</guid><description>Vì sao chúng ta khoan hẵn đầu tư 1. Vẫn còn nợ xấu Nợ thẻ tín dụng Vay mua xe, nhà, cá nhân, tiêu dùng</description></item><item><title>MINIMALISM</title><link>https://lehanget154.github.io/minimalism/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://lehanget154.github.io/minimalism/</guid><description>What is minimalism? A minimalist intentionally focuses on what really matters. For some, this means eliminating the ‘stuff’ that doesn’t make you happy. Minimalism is the intentional choice to live with less. Minimalism is not a lack of something. It&amp;rsquo;s simply the perfect amount of something. On the contrary with minimalism is consumerism. Benefits of minimalism: Less is more Time: Less time to do house chores. More time to build hobbies, habits, knowledge Money: Less consumerism, more saving Freedom: Freedom from fear, worry, overwhelm, depression Improve life&amp;rsquo;s quality: Buy less but high quality, focus on quality than quantity Minimalism spirit Minimalism is a journey where we sàng lọc dần things that do not bring up any values để chúng ta không phải tốn năng lượng vô ích vô những thứ đó nữa.</description></item></channel></rss>